Guna Ranjani Katuri

Old Madiwala Road,Sandhya Theatre, 560068, Bangalore, Karnataka gunaranjani.jakkula@gmail.com 8341240568

Summary

A leads generation specialist is a professional who collects and evaluates potential sales opportunities. They often work for companies who focus on selling their products or services to other businesses.

I have Experienced in generating contacts from the industries (IT, Law firms, Real Estate, Pharmaceutical, Biotechnology, Schools, Universities, Construction, Mortgage, Financial Services, Recruiting, Automotive, Insurance, Manufacturing, Retail, Marketing & Advertising, Events, Tradeshows, Podcasts, Accounting, etc.,)

Education

Eluru College of Engineering & Technology

Computer Science of Engineering (B.Tech) • Eluru, Andhra Pradesh

04/2017

Experience

Bizrak Web Solutions

Lead Generator Researcher/ Team Lead • Eluru, Andhra Pradesh

04/2018 - 05/2022

May 2018 - November 2020

Lead Generation Researcher:

I offer a wider range of Internet research, LinkedIn lead generation, Data Entry, email sourcing and contact list building service. I enjoy working from all over the globe, from the US to CA to UK to Australia to India..

So on these base I have 4 years of experience in LG research, I am use multiple growth strategies via LinkedIn, Facebook, Email marketing, etc. to generate qualify leads based on requirements...

December 2020 - May 2022

Team Lead:

- 1) Liaison between customers and lead generation team.
- 2) In charge of a team of 20 people based in Eluru.
- 3) Providing guidance, instruction and direction for the purpose of achieving result, grant quality standards.
- 4) Managing individual and group coaching/training activities also.

Skills

Quality lead generation, Qualifying and prospecting leads, Research and reports generation, Best Research for quality data

Languages

English, Telugu